Good morning everyone, first of all
to install iBill Tech Care we have to go to the Play Store,
go like this in the Play Store,
after that a search button is shown at the top,
in the search button you can write aa
elite tech care l in tech care like tech
care, after that search,
after searching scroll up a little and
go to the second option iBill
Tech Care Insurance, click here, it
is showing open here because I have already
installed it, you guys will find it
written install in it, you guys install it,
after installing it, we will see an
open option like this,
give it to me, I have to enter it,
[music]
3261261 62
what is it, you
can do it later,
definitely
limited
policy number, this seems wrong, you will have to enter the policy number, after entering the
policy number, click on the
submit button that comes at the bottom,
after that such details will start showing,
policy number etc. till when is its
validity and how much amount and how much did it cost,
all the details